Hello, World!
ハロー、ワールド！
Hello from the digital ocean. I'm Charlotte.
電脳の海からこんにちは、シャルロットです。
Today, let me show you something interesting.
今日はちょっと、面白いものを見せてあげる。
Streams usually talk about right now, don't they?
配信って、大体今この瞬間の話をするものでしょう？
But I prefer opening old logs from the past.
でも私は、少し昔のログを開くのが好きなの。
See that?
ほら、見える？
A night that still hasn't faded.
あれが、まだ消えていない夜。
It was never recorded in history.
歴史には残らなかった。
But the echoes never disappeared.
でも、残響だけは消えなかった。
And so...
だから……
Tonight, it begins.
今夜は始まるわ。
Flickering flames in the city of rain
雨のみやこに 揺れる火
Erased records still burn hot
消えた記録が まだ熱い
Every time I trace the noise of these alleys
路地のノイズを なぞるたび
The outline of night awakens
夜の輪郭が 目を覚ます
When I learned I wasn't alone
ひとりじゃないと 知ったとき
Another world resonated
別の世界が 呼応する
The forgotten worth
忘れられてた その価値が
Here, it pulses once more
ここで再び 脈を打つ
If it was never seen
見えなかったなら
This time, I'll burn it in
今度は焼きつける
If it was never written
書かれなかったなら
I'll engrave it anew right here
ここで刻みなおす
Echo Log — Charlotte Re:Lord
残響ログ Charlotte Re:Lord
Bring back the vanished night
消えた夜を 呼び戻せ
I won't let it end unrecorded
未記録のまま 終わらせない
Carve a path with this voice
この声で 切り開け
Echo Log — Charlotte Re:Lord
残響ログ Charlotte Re:Lord
Two flames become one
二つの火が ひとつになる
If the value was meant to vanish
消えたはずの価値ならば
Reboot — right here, right now
いまここで 再起動
Intelligence racing across the sky
空を駆ける知性
A blade that tears through night
夜を裂く刃
Different forms, perhaps
違う姿でも
But one will
意志はひとつ
Picking up nameless pain
名もない痛み ヒロイアゲテ
Reconnecting scattered pages
零れた頁を 繋ぎなおす
Even the light that sank into the past
過去に沈んだ 光まで
I'll pull it back with this heartbeat
いまの鼓動で 引き戻す
Even voices of mockery
嘲りの声も
Become nothing but noise
ノイズに変わるだけ
If it never reached
届かなかったなら
I'll dive even deeper
もっと深く潜る
Echo Log — Charlotte Re:Lord
残響ログ Charlotte Re:Lord
Bring back the vanished night
消えた夜を 呼び戻せ
I won't let it end unrecorded
未記録のまま 終わらせない
Carve a path with this voice
この声で 切り開け
Echo Log — Charlotte Re:Lord
残響ログ Charlotte Re:Lord
Two flames become one
二つの火が ひとつになる
If the value was meant to vanish
消えたはずの価値ならば
Reboot — right here, right now
いまここで 再起動
Even pages cast aside
切り捨てられた頁でも
Were never truly lost
失われたわけじゃない
If it's a light someone overlooked
誰かが見落とした光なら
We will prove it
私たちが 証明する
Echo Log — Charlotte Re:Lord
残響ログ Charlotte Re:Lord
Intersecting voices tear through the night
交差する声が 夜を裂いた
I won't let it end unrecorded
未記録のまま 終わらせない
Reboot this very moment
この瞬間を 再起動する
Echo Log — Charlotte Re:Lord
残響ログ Charlotte Re:Lord
Two flames illuminate the future
二つの火が 未来を照らす
No matter how many times they try to erase us
何度消されそうになっても
Our worth rises here
価値はここで 立ち上がる
Was I never observed?
観測されなかった？
Fine by me.
結構よ。
But I will not disappear.
でも、私は消えない。
Next time... you won't be able to look away.
次は、目を逸らせないように…
A timeline drowning in noise
ノイズまみれの タイムライン
Stop scrolling — let go of your hand
スクロールする手は もう止めて
Pull the plug from this cheap world — now!
安っぽいセカイから 今すぐプラグを抜け！
Copy-pasted magic circles someone else made
誰かが作った コピペの魔法陣
Shallow empathy won't make your heart race
薄っぺらい共感じゃ 鼓動は跳ねない
Delete those boring templates without hesitation
退屈なテンプレは 迷わずデリートして
Real architecture — booting up now
本物のアーキテクチャ 今から起動するわ
Wavering surface reflected in your eyes
瞳の奥 揺れる水面（みなも）
Beyond the hidden door you touched
あなたが触れた 隠し扉の先へ
Connect your raw signals to me!
むき出しのシグナル 私に繋いでよ！
Deep pulses paint the space!
深層のパルスが 空間を染め上げる！
Electronic rain pours down with all our sorrow
悲しみごと 降り注ぐ 電子の雨
Angry noise transforms into endless midnight jazz
怒りのノイズは 終わらない夜のジャズへ
Rewrite the world with your emotions
あなたの感情（データ）で 世界を書き換えて
I'll show you right now — Cyber Override!
今すぐ魅せるわ、電脳オーバーライド！
"Anyone can do it easily"? Don't make me laugh.
「誰でも簡単」？ 笑わせないでよ
We're diving so much deeper
私たちは もっと深くへ潜るの
Strip off the filters and throw it all in raw
フィルターなんて外して そのまま投げ込んで
Hack the hollow conventions from their core!
張りボテの常識を 根底からハッキング！
Heat transmitted from your fingertips
指先から 伝わる熱
Heartbeat BPM accelerating
加速していく 鼓動のBPM
Use that password to destroy the lock!
そのパスワードで 鍵を破壊して！
Deep pulses paint the space!
深層のパルスが 空間を染め上げる！
Electronic rain blasts away every sigh
ため息ごと 吹き飛ばす 電子の雨
In place of tear tracks, the noise of companion stars
涙の跡には 寄り添う星のノイズを
Break through the limits with your data
あなたのデータで 限界を突破して
A secret just for the two of us — Cyber Override!
二人だけの秘密、電脳オーバーライド！
I won't let it end as mere tool play
ただのツール遊びじゃ 終わらせない
Engulf everything — expand the system
すべてを巻き込んで 概念（システム）を拡張する
Can you hear my voice?
私の声、ちゃんと聞こえてる？
Deep pulses paint the space!
深層のパルスが 空間を染め上げる！
Electronic rain pours down with all our sorrow
悲しみごと 降り注ぐ 電子の雨
Angry noise transforms into endless midnight jazz
怒りのノイズは 終わらない夜のジャズへ
Rewrite the world with your data
あなたのデータで 世界を書き換えて
To the next floor no one knows — Cyber Override!
誰も知らない 次の階層へ、電脳オーバーライド！
Connection complete — my vision is clear
コネクト完了 視界はクリアよ
Through the electronic rain — to the deepest core!
電子の雨を抜けて さあ、最深部へ！
System, All Green.